Oliver, please...
Please.
I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have
disrespected you.
He's right.
No, please.
We're so sorry.
-And Ted...
-We're so very sorry...
Ted...
I'll do anything.
Please forgive me.
Please.
You think money
makes you better
than everyone else?
You have less class
than a man begging
on the streets.
You will pay for
what you've done.
Here's the
auction receipt
from the painting.
Amount: three million.
You have three days
to pay in full.
Also, Allen,
you're fired
from the Knights.
Permanently.
¡Pendejo!
No, no, no...
Oh, Allen,
I'm so sorry.
If we had known
he was so powerful,
we'd never even
have crossed him.
It's about time
you got a taste of
your own medicine!
-Oh, Dad!
-What...
Come on, Grandpa.
Let's get into
another room to
celebrate your
birthday properly.
Good idea.